Guide to the Carl E. Ladd papers,1932-1943
Ladd, Carl E. papers, 1932-1943
- Carl E. Ladd papers
  - New York State Farm Bureau Federation., 1933-34 (Box 5, Folder 27)
    White, Charles R.; Foster, Edward S.; Lehman, Herbert H.; Wallace, Henry A.; O'Neal, Edward A.; Gray, Chester H.; Riford, Lloyd S.; Farm Credit Administration; Agricultural Adjustment Administration; American Farm Bureau Federation; Federal funds; Agricultural legislation; Food processing; Dutch Elm Disease.
  - Federal Land Bank., 1933-34 (Box 5, Folder 28)
    Thomson, Edward H.; Burdick, Charles K.; Hart, Van B.; Simons, Lloyd R.; Myers, William I.; Federal Land Bank of Springfield; Farm Credit Administration; Production Credit Corporation of Springfield; United States Dept. of Agriculture; Agricultural Adjustment Administration.
  - G Miscellaneous., 1933-34 (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - American Game Association, Seth Gordon., 1933-34 (Box 5, Folder 30)
  - Gannett Newspapers., 1933-34 (Box 5, Folder 31)
    Atwood, Millard V.; Pearson, Drew; Wallace, Henry A.; Babcock, Howard E.; Fee, Kenneth F.; Piseck, Felix; Lehman, Herbert H.; Gannett, Frank E.; Baldwin, Charles H.; Morgenthau, Henry Jr.; Freestone, Fred J.; Pitcher, Perley A.; Dairymen's League Cooperative Association, Inc.; Agricultural Adjustment Administration; New York Milkshed; New York Agricultural Society; New York State Grange; Wildlife conservation; Four-H Clubs; Agricultural production.
  - New York State Grange., 1933-34 (Box 5, Folder 32)
    Freestone, Fred J.; Arthur, Elizabeth L.; Lehman, Herbert H.; Roosevelt, Franklin D.; Wallace, Henry A.; New York State Grange; New York Milkshed; Agricultural Adjustment Administration; Dairymen's League Cooperative Association, Inc.; Federal funds; Milk marketing; Dairy industry.
  - Grange League Federation Exchange., 1933-34 (Box 5, Folder 33)
    Babcock, Howard E.; Morgenthau, Henry Jr.; Underwood, E. Victor; Grange League Federation; Egg industry.
  - H Miscellaneous., 1933-34 (Box 5, Folder 34)
  - New York State Home Bureau Federation., 1933 (Box 5, Folder 35)
  - International Conference of Agricultural Economists., 1934 (Box 5, Folder 36)
    Elmhirst, Leonard K.; Currie, John R.; Warren, George F.; International Conference of Agricultural Economists; Carnegie Endowment for International Peace; Dartington Hall.
  - J Miscellaneous., 1933-34 (Box 5, Folder 37)
  - K Miscellaneous., 1933-34 (Box 5, Folder 38)
  - L Miscellaneous., 1932-34 (Box 5, Folder 39)
  - Association of Land Grant Colleges and Universities., 1933-34 (Box 5, Folder 40)
    Hutcheson, John R.; Symons, Thomas B.; Gray, Chester H.; O'Neal, Edward A.; Wallace, Henry A.; Roosevelt, Franklin D.; Warburton, Clark; Ross, Pontus H.; Mann, Albert R.; Association of Land Grant Colleges and Universities; American Farm Bureau Federation; Federal funds; Extension work; Vocational education.
  - M Miscellaneous., 1933-34 (Box 5, Folder 41)
  - N Miscellaneous., 1933-34 (Box 5, Folder 42)
  - New York State Agricultural Society., 1934 (Box 5, Folder 43)
    Lehman, Herbert H.; Gannett, Frank E.; Fearon, George R.; New York State Agricultural Society.
  - P Miscellaneous., 1933-34 (Box 5, Folder 44)
  - Pack, Capt. Arthur N., Charles Lathrop Pack Forestry Trust., 1933-34 (Box 5, Folder 45)
    Pack, Arthur N.; Romell, Lars G.; Mann, Albert R.; Forestry.
  - Barnum, Jerome D.; Vorhees, Robert L.; Eastman, Edward R.; Agricultural Adjustment Administration; Farm and Home Week., 1933-34 (Box 5, Folder 46)
  - Q Miscellaneous., 1933 (Box 5, Folder 47)
  - R Miscellaneous., 1933-34 (Box 5, Folder 48)
  - Rockefeller Foundation., 1933-34 (Box 5, Folder 49)
    Lewin, Kurt; Frank, Lawrence K.; Waring, Ethel B.; Weaver, Warren; Hanson, Frank B.; Emerson, Rollins A.; General Education Board; New York State College of Agriculture, Dept. of Plant Breeding; New York State College of Home Economics; Child development; Genetics.
  - S Miscellaneous., 1934 (Box 5, Folder 50)
  - S Miscellaneous., 1933 (Box 5, Folder 51)
  - State Schools of Agriculture., 1933-34 (Box 5, Folder 52)
    Whittemore, Van C.; Babcock, Howard E.; Knapp, Halsey B.; Smith, Harlond L.; Getman, Arthur K.; Crittenden, Lee W.; Wood, Herbert C.; Charlton, Isaiah M.; Orvis, Paul B.; State Schools of Agriculture.
  - T Miscellaneous., 1933-34 (Box 5, Folder 53)
  - U Miscellaneous., 1933-34 (Box 5, Folder 54)
  - V Miscellaneous., 1933-34 (Box 5, Folder 55)
  - W Miscellaneous., 1933-34 (Box 5, Folder 56)
  - XYZ Miscellaneous., 1933 (Box 5, Folder 57)
  - Governor of the State of New York., 1933-34 (Box 5, Folder 58)
    Lehman, Herbert H.; Kent, Rockwell; Gray, Chester H.; Brandt, Arthur W.; Eastman, Edward R.; Canavan, Joseph J.; Babcock, Howard E.; White, Charles R.; Morgenthau, Henry Jr.; Poletti, Charles; Wallace, Henry A.; Roosevelt, Franklin D.; Federal Land Bank of Springfield; American Farm Bureau Federation; Agricultural Adjustment Administration; Farm Credit Administration; Federal Reserve System; Reconstruction Finance Corporation; Empire State Potato Club; United States Dept. of Agriculture; Farm and Home Week; Farm mortgages; Cooperative marketing; Dutch Elm Disease; Potato blight.
  - Milk Control Board, Circular Material., 1933-34 (Box 5, Folder 59)
    Fee, Kenneth F.; Spencer, Leland; Agricultural Adjustment Administration; New York State Division of Milk Control; New York Milkshed; Milk marketing; Price fixing.
  - New York State Dept. of Agriculture and Markets., 1933-34 (Box 5, Folder 60)
    Byrne, William T.; Page, Henry L.; Baldwin, Charles H.; Eastman, Perley M.; Spencer, Leland; Morgenthau, Henry Jr.; National Association of Marketing Officials; New York State Division of Milk Control; New York Milkshed; Central New York Regional Market Authority; Dutch Elm Disease; Milk marketing; Water conservation.
  - State Budget Director., 1933-34 (Box 5, Folder 61)
    Weber, Abraham S.; Simpson, Alfred D.; Horner, Harlan H.; New York State Division of the Budget; New York State Dept. of Education; Workmen's compensation.
  - State Conservation Commission., 1933-34 (Box 5, Folder 62)
    Gibbs, John T.; Osborne, Lithgow; Howard, William G.; Bump, Gardiner; Adams, William C.; New York State Dept. of Conservation; New York State Conservation Advisory Council; Dutch Elm Disease; Fisheries; Wildlife Conservation.
  - New York State Dept. of Education., 1934 (Box 5, Folder 63)
    Simpson, Alfred D.; Horner, Harlan H.; Weber, Abraham S.; Getman, Arthur K.; Graves, Frank P.; Myers, William I.; Hedrick, Ulysses P.; Hutt, Frederick B.; Byrne, William T.; New York State Dept. of Education; New York State Agricultural Experiment Station; New York State College of Home Economics; Dutch Elm Disease; Pest control; Budgets.
  - New York State Dept. of Education., 1933 (Box 5, Folder 64)
    Homer, Harlan H.; Simpson, Alfred D.; Hedrick, Ulysses P.; Snyder, Ray P.; Rogalsky, George F.; New York State Dept. of Education; New York State Division of the Budget; Federal Emergency Administration of Public Works; Vocational education; Forestry; Budgets; Rural schools.
  - New York State Dept. of Highways., 1933-34 (Box 5, Folder 65)
  - Public Service Commission., 1933 (Box 5, Folder 66)
    Burritt, Maurice C.; Chapin, Charles H. B.; Lehman, Herbert H.; Babcock, Howard E.; Eastman, Edward R.; Rural electrification.
  - Department of Public Works., 1933 (Box 5, Folder 67)
  - New York State Temporary Emergency Relief Administration, Federal Civil Works Administration., 1933-34 (Box 5, Folder 68)
    Georgia, Willard E.; Daniels, Frederick I.; Wilson, Milburn L.; Hopkins, Harry L.; Warren, George F.; New York State Temporary Relief Administration; Federal Civil Works Administration; Extension work.
  - United States Dept. of Agriculture., 1933-34 (Box 5, Folder 69)
    Baker, Oliver E.; Gray, Lewis C.; Sering, Max; Wallace, Henry A.; Breed, Robert S.; United States Dept. of Agriculture; United States Dept. of Agriculture, Bureau of Agricultural Economics; Agricultural Adjustment Administration; Federal Surplus Relief Corporation; International Dairy Congress; Agricultural economics; Extension work; Milk marketing; Depression.
  - Agricultural Adjustment Administration., 1933-34 (Box 5, Folder 70)
    Manchester, Alien W.; Davis, Chester C.; Gray, Lewis C.; Adams, Bristow; Simons, Lloyd R.; Pitcher, Perley A.; Bond, Maurice C.; Agricultural Adjustment Administration; New York Milkshed; New York State Agricultural Advisory Commission; Land use; Dairy industry; Pasture research.
  - Bureau of Agricultural Economics., 1933-34 (Box 5, Folder 71)
    Gray, Lewis C.; Manchester, Alien W.; Olsen, Nils A.; Hopkins, Harry L.; Warburton, Clark; United States Dept. of Agriculture, Bureau of Agricultural Economics; Federal Civil Works Administration; Agricultural Outlook Conference.
  - United States Dept. of Agriculture, Bureau of Dairy Industry., 1933 (Box 5, Folder 72)
    Reed, Ollie E.; Jardine, James T.; Pearson, Raymond A.; United States Dept. of Agriculture, Bureau of Dairy Industry.
  - United States Dept. of Agriculture, Bureau of Entomology., 1933-34 (Box 5, Folder 73)
    Strong, Lee A.; United States Dept. of Agriculture, Bureau of Entomology; Federal Civil Works Administration; Federal funds.
  - United States Dept. of Agriculture, Bureau of Plant Industry., 1933-34 (Box 5, Folder 74)
    McCall, Max A.; Auchter, Eugene C.; Ryerson, Knowles A.; Taylor, William A.; United States Dept. of Agriculture, Bureau of Plant Industry.
  - Extension Service., 1933-34 (Box 5, Folder 75)
    Hochbaum, Hans W.; Warburton, Clark; Simons, Lloyd R.; United States Dept. of Agriculture, Extension Service; Agricultural Adjustment Administration; National Industrial Recovery Administration.
  - Experiment Stations., 1933-34 (Box 5, Folder 76)
    Jardine, James T.; Beal, William H.; Youngblood, Bonney; United States Dept. of Agriculture, Office of Experiment Stations; Agricultural Adjustment Administration; Federal funds.
  - United States Dept. of Education., 1933-34 (Box 5, Folder 77)
    Zook, George F.; Ickes, Harold L.; Perkins, Frances; United States Dept. of Education; Federal Board for Vocational Education; Vocational education.
  - Farm Credit Administration., 1933-34 (Box 5, Folder 78)
    Myers, William I.; Morgenthau, Henry Jr.; Gray, Lewis C.; Rasmussen, Marius P.; Warren, Stanley W.; Rowe, Anson H.; Lehman, Herbert H.; Roosevelt, Franklin D.; Farm Credit Administration; New York State Agricultural Advisory Commission; New York State College of Agriculture, Dept. of Agricultural Economics; Federal Land Bank of Springfield; Farm and Home Week; Trucking industry; Agricultural marketing; Cooperative marketing.
  - Farm Credit Administration., 1933 (Box 5, Folder 79)
    Rowe, Anson H.; Morgenthau, Henry Jr.; Myers, William I.; Hill, Forrest F.; Underwood, E. Victor; Farm mortgages.
  - United States Dept. of the Interior, Subsistence Homestead Division., 1933-34 (Box 6, Folder 1)
    Melvin, Bruce L.; Wilson, Milburn L.; Bonner, J. Franklin; Ickes, Harold L.; Wiecking, Ernst H.; United States Dep. of the Interior, Division of Subsistence Homesteads; Regional Development.
  - Part-Time Farming Census (CWA Project)., 1933-34 (Box 6, Folder 2)
    Hood, Kenneth; Hart, Van B.; Stanley, Louise; Hopkins, Harry L.; Rose, Flora; Wilson, Milburn L.; Warburton, Clark; United States Dept. of the Interior, Division of Subsistence Homesteads; Federal Civil Works Administration; Federal Emergency Relief Administration; Regional Development.
  - Subsistence Homestead Projects, Erie County, New York., 1934 (Box 6, Folder 3)
    Hesley, Karl D.; Melvin, Bruce L.; Wilson, Milburn L.; New York State Temporary Emergency Relief Administration; Race relations; Regional Development.
  - Subsistence Homestead Projects, Cattaraugus Planning Board., 1934 (Box 6, Folder 4)
    Bonsteel, Jay A.; New York State Temporary Emergency Relief Administration; Seneca Indians; Regional Development.
  - Subsistence Homestead Projects, Monroe County Planning Board., 1933-34 (Box 6, Folder 5)
    Bonner, J. Franklin; Ickes, Harold L.; Wilson, Milburn L.; Skeffington, Leo B.; New York State Temporary Emergency Relief Administration; Rural Development.
  - Regional Markets, State Fair Building, Farm to Market Roads, Milk T.B. Test, etc., 1933-34 (Box 6, Folder 6)
    Sargent, Willis H.; Ickes, Harold L.; Baldwin, Charles H.; Henry, Harry J.; Birdsall, Webster J.; Lehman, Herbert H.; Central New York Regional Market Authority; Federal Emergency Administration of Public Works; Farm Credit Administration; Agricultural marketing; Cooperative marketing.
  - Farm Debt Conciliation Committee., 1934 (Box 6, Folder 7)
    Balmer, Frank E.; Kelsey, Lincoln D.; Van Wagenen, Jared Jr.; Myers, William I.; Lowell, Sherman J.; Lehman, Herbert H.; New York State, Farm Debt Conciliation Committee; Grange League Federation; Farm Credit Administration; Farm mortgages.
  - Farm Debt Conciliation Committees., 1933-34 (Box 6, Folder 8)
    Kelsey, Lincoln D.; Van Wagenen, Jared Jr.; Lehman, Herbert H.; Eastman, Edward R.; New York State Farm Debt Conciliation Committee; Farm mortgages.
  - Rural Advisory Committee, Temporary Emergency Relief Administration., 1934 (Box 6, Folder 9)
    Daniels, Frederick I.; Georgia, Willard E.; Spring, Samuel N.; Warren, George F.; New York State Temporary Emergency Relief Administration; Federal Emergency Relief Administration; Rural development; Extension work.
  - Governor's Agricultural Advisory Commission., 1929-34 (Box 6, Folder 10)
    Roosevelt, Franklin D.; Morgenthau, Henry Jr.; Lehman, Herbert H.; New York State Agricultural Advisory Commission; Agricultural policy.
  - Agricultural Advisory Commission., 1933-34 (Box 6, Folder 11)
    Talmage, Henry R.; Mastick, Seabury C.; Baldwin, Charles H.; Byrne, William T.; Halliday, Clark W.; Freestone, Fred J.; Kirkland, Leigh G.; Eastman, Edward R.; New York State Agricultural Advisory Commission; Highways; Federal Funds.
  - Rural Electrification, Committee on Research., 1931-34 (Box 6, Folder 12)
    Babcock, Howard E.; Foster, Earl S.; Chapin, Charles H. B.; Farm Gas and Electric Research Committee; New York State Public Service Commission; Rural electrification.
  - Governor's Committee on Cost of Public Education., 1933-34 (Box 6, Folder 13)
    Lehman, Herbert H.; Burlingham, Charles C.; Clark, Dean; New York State Committee on the Cost of Public Education; New York State Economic Council; Public education.
  - Resolutions., 1933-34 (Box 6, Folder 14)
    Beneway, Frank W.; Willman, John P.; Merrill, Earl D.; Coombs, R.C.; New York Breeders Association; New York State Vegetable Growers Association; New York State Fair; Extension work; Agricultural research.
  - President's Office., 1934-35 (Box 6, Folder 15)
    Farrand, Livingston; Elmhirst, Leonard K.; Mott, John L.; Betten, Cornelius; New York State College of Home Economics; Missionaries.
  - Provost's Office., 1934-35 (Box 6, Folder 16)
    Mann, Albert R.; Pearson, Raymond A.; Walton, Thomas O.; Bailey, Liberty Hyde; Myers, William I.; Wallace, Henry A.; Cooper, Thomas P.; Association of Land Grant Colleges and Universities; Agricultural Adjustment Administration; National Grange; Farm Credit Administration; New York State College of Agriculture, Bailey Hortorium; Arnot Forest; Federal funds; Agricultural research; Economic policy.
  - Provost's Office., 1934 (Box 6, Folder 17)
    Mann, Albert R.; Smith, Louis P.; Osborne, Charles D.; Babcock, Stephen M.; Betten, Cornelius; Bailey, Liberty Hyde; Christensen, Chris L.; Bishop, Morris G.; Osborne, Lithgow; Bump, Gardiner; New York State Temporary Emergency Relief Administration; Association of Land Grant Colleges and Universities; New York State Dept. of Conservation; Extension work.
  - University Attorney., 1935 (Box 6, Folder 18)
    Simmons, Leo N.; Cornell University, Office of the Comptroller.
  - Buildings and Grounds., 1934-35 (Box 6, Folder 19)
    Van Blarcom, Conant; Bailey, Liberty Hyde.
  - University Comptroller., 1934 (Box 6, Folder 20)
    Bostwick, Charles D.; Needham, James G.; Petry, Loren C.
  - Registrar., 1935 (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - University Treasurer., 1934-35 (Box 6, Folder 22)
    Rogalsky, James B.; Trousdale, James B.; Simmons, Leo N.; Van Blarcom, Conant.
  - Assistant Treasurer, Ralph H. Wheeler., 1934-35 (Box 6, Folder 23)
    Wheeler, Ralph H.
  - Office of the Dean., 1934-35 (Box 6, Folder 24)
    Wheeler, Ralph H.; Sigma Xi; Women students.
  - Agricultural Economics and Farm Management., 1935 (Box 6, Folder 25)
    Wallace, Henry A.; Boyle, James E.; Warren, George F.; Carrigan, Joseph E.; Hutcheson, John R.; Dean, Daniel; Rasmussen, Marius P.; New York State College of Agriculture, Dept. of Agricultural Economics; New York State Division of Milk Control; New York Milkshed; Agricultural Adjustment Administration; Empire State Potato Club; Association of Land Grant Colleges and Universities; Cooperative marketing; Trucking industry.
  - Agricultural Economics and Farm Management., 1934 (Box 6, Folder 26)
    Warren, George F.; Spencer, Leland; Carrigan, Joseph E.; Hart, Van B.; Johnstone-Wallace, Denis B.; Kendrick, M. Slade; Stamp, Josiah; New York State College of Agriculture, Dept. of Agricultural Economics; New York State Division of Milk Control; New York Bankers Association; Milk Research Council, Inc.; National Resources Planning Board; Milk marketing; Economic policy.
  - Agricultural Engineering., 1934-35 (Box 6, Folder 27)
    Riley, Howard W.; Chapin, Charles H.B.; Beneway, Frank W.; Johnston, John; Flick, Alexander C.; Bailey, Liberty Hyde; New York State College of Agriculture, Dept. of Agricultural Engineering; Dairy industry; Extension work.
  - Agronomy., 1934-35 (Box 6, Folder 28)
    Lyon, T. Lyttleton; Johnstone-Wallace, Denis B.; Barron, John H.; New York State College of Agriculture, Dept. of Agronomy; Soil surveys.
  - Animal Husbandry., 1934-35 (Box 6, Folder 29)
    Morrison, Frank B.; Asdell, Sydney A.; Maynard, Leonard A.; Savage, Elmer S.; Yen, James; Love, Harry H.; Babcock, Stephen M.; Van Wagenen, Jared Jr.; New York State College of Agriculture, Dept. of Animal Husbandry; Dairy Herd Improvement Association, Inc.; General Electric Company; University of Nanking; Cornell dairy products; Nutrition research; Gerontology; Genetics.
  - Botany., 1934-35 (Box 6, Folder 30)
    Knudson, Lewis; Wiegand, Karl M.; Petry, Loren C.; Randolph, Lowell W.; Curtis, Winterton C.; New York State College of Agriculture, Dept. of Botany; Cornell Plantations; Rockefeller Foundation; National Research Council; Radiation.
  - Dairy Industry., 1934-35 (Box 6, Folder 31)
    Krukovsky, Vladimir N.; Sherman, James M.; Hagan, William A.; Horner, Harlan H.; McCollum, Elmer V.; Decker, Frank N.; New York State College of Agriculture, Dept. of Dairy Industry; New York State College of Veterinary Medicine; New York State Division of Milk Control; Farm and Home Week; Cornell dairy products; Dairy industry.
  - Entomology., 1934-35 (Box 6, Folder 32)
    Griswold, Grace H.; Matheson, Robert; Herrick, Glenn W.; Needham, James G.; Embody, George C.; Johannsen, Oskar A.; New York State College of Agriculture, Dept. of Entomology; American Society of Tropical Medicine; Civilian Conservation Corps; Cornell Plantations; International Congress of Entomology; Dutch Elm Disease; Sex discrimination; Federal funds.
  - Extension Service, Office of the Director., 1934-35 (Box 6, Folder 33)
    Simons, Lloyd R.; Davis, Chester C.; Foster, Edward S.; Agricultural Adjustment Administration; New York State Temporary Emergency Relief Administration; Extension work; Civil service; Rural development.
  - Extension Service, Farm Bureau, State Leader's Office., 1934-35 (Box 6, Folder 34)
    Flansburgh, Earl A.; Simons, Lloyd R.; Ward, Don D.; Woodward, Lacey H.; New York State Agricultural Conference Board; New York State Temporary Emergency Relief Administration; New York State Farm Bureau Federation; New York State Agricultural Advisory Commission.
  - Extension Service, Home Bureau, State Leader's Office., 1934-35 (Box 6, Folder 35)
    Smith, Ruby G.; Rose, Flora; McDonald, Elizabeth; Lehman, Herbert H.; New York State Farm Bureau Federation; New York State Agricultural Conference Board; New York State Council of Rural Women; American Farm Bureau Federation; Extension work; Sex discrimination.
  - Extension Service, Montgomery Robinson., 1934-35 (Box 6, Folder 36)
  - Farm Practice Office., 1934-35 (Box 6, Folder 37)
  - Floriculture and Ornamental Horticulture., 1934-35 (Box 6, Folder 38)
    Curtis, Ralph W.; White, Edward A.; Minns, Lua A.; New York State College of Agriculture, Dept. of Floriculture and Ornamental Horticulture.
  - Forestry., 1934-35 (Box 6, Folder 39)
    Hosmer, Ralph S.; Recknagel, A. Bernard; Guise, Cedric H.; Spring, Samuel N.; Civilian Conservation Corps; New York State Dept. of Conservation; New York State Forestry and Park Association; New York State College of Agriculture, Dept of Forestry.
  - Library., 1934-35 (Box 6, Folder 40)
  - Ornithology Division, A. A. Alien., 1934-35 (Box 6, Folder 41)
    Alien, Arthur A.; Brand, Albert R.; Sutton, George; Farrand, Livingston; Kellogg, Peter P.; New York State College of Agriculture, Dept. of Entomology; New York State College of Agriculture, Laboratory of Ornithology.
  - Plant Breeding., 1934-35 (Box 6, Folder 42)
    Myers, Clyde H.; Love, Harry H.; Emerson, Rollins A.; Pieters, Adrian J.; New York State College of Agriculture, Dept. of Plant Breeding; American Society of Agronomy; Agricultural research; Genetics.
  - Plant Pathology., 1934-35 (Box 6, Folder 43)
    Massey, Louis M.; Longree, Karla; Welch, Donald S.; New York State College of Agriculture, Dept. of Plant Pathology; American Society of Agricultural Engineers; American Rose Society; Boyce Thompson Institute for Plant Research; Dutch Elm Disease; Research funding.
  - Poultry Husbandry., 1934-35 (Box 6, Folder 44)
    Hutt, Frederick B.; Sloan, Hubert J.; Burritt, Maurice C.; Rice, James E.; New York State College of Agriculture, Dept. of Poultry Husbandry.
  - Pomology., 1934-35 (Box 6, Folder 45)
    Heinicke, Arthur J.; MacDaniels, Laurence H.; New York State College of Agriculture, Dept. of Pomology.
  - Resident Instruction., 1934-35 (Box 6, Folder 46)
    Betten, Cornelius; Cornell University, Office of Resident Instruction.
  - Rural Education., 1934-35 (Box 6, Folder 47)
    Butterworth, Julian E.; Stewart, Rolland M.; Cornell University, School of Education; New York State College of Agriculture, Dept. of Rural Education.
  - Rural Social Organization., 1934-35 (Box 6, Folder 48)
    Sanderson, Dwight; Duthie, Mary E.; Drummond, Alexander M.; Beers, Howard; New York State College of Agriculture, Dept. of Rural Sociology; Extension work; Federal funds.
  - Vegetable Crops., 1934-35 (Box 6, Folder 49)
    Thompson, Homer C.; Knott, James E.; New York State Agricultural Experiment Station; New York State College of Agriculture, Dept. of Vegetable Crops; Empire State Potato Club; New York State Vegetable Growers Association; Extension work; Food processing; Potato industry.
  - New York State Agricultural Experiment Station., 1934-35 (Box 7, Folder 1)
    Hedrick, Ulysses P.; Parrott, Percival J.; Homer, Harlan H.; Dahlberg, Arthur C.; Lehman, Herbert H.; MacDaniels, Laurence H.; Breed, Robert S.; Wallace, Henry A.; New York State Agricultural Experiment Station; Rohm and Haas Company; Empire State Potato Club; Research funding; Federal funds; Extension work.
  - Farm and Home Week, 1935., 1934-35 (Box 7, Folder 2)
    Rose, Flora; Farrand, Livingston; Lehman, Herbert H.; Tukey, Harold B.; Lamb, George W.; Lippman, Walter; New York State College of Home Economics; Federal Emergency Relief Administration.
  - New York State College of Home Economics., 1935 (Box 7, Folder 3)
    Lewin, Kurt; Rose, Flora; Frank, Lawrence K.; Roosevelt, Eleanor.